- Hey.  - Hey.
-嘿   -嘿
We're here to say goodbye.
我们来道别
We're off to Ohio.
要去俄亥俄州
Oh, right, your adoption interview.
对哦  领养面谈
Yep. We'll meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.
是啊  我们去见未来我们孩儿他妈
I can't believe it. When you come back,
难以置信  你们回来时
you'll have a baby. That is so weird.
会带着婴儿  太奇怪了
And so incorrect.
也很不正确
She's only a couple months pregnant.
她只怀孕几个月
She liked our application
她选中了我们的申请表
but might not like us.
是否喜欢我们还不一定
Come on, she's gonna love you guys.
她会喜欢你们的
Thank you.
谢谢
But we're trying not to get our hopes up.
但我们尽量不期望过高
A lot could still get in our way.
还有很多事情挡在我们面前
She could decide against adoption,
她可能会决定拒绝把孩子给人领养
like another couple better.
也可能选中其他夫妇
What are you gonna name it?
你们打算给小孩取啥名字
I could develop a condition
我就有这个本事
in which I talk and talk
费尽口舌
and no one hears a word.
而旁人却充耳不闻
But just think, okay? What if everything goes right?
试想  如果一切顺利
What if this woman does pick you guys?
如果她真选了你们俩呢
Oh, my God. She's gonna pick us!
天  那她就会选我们
So we're standing firm on
我们决心
"not getting our hopes up"?
决不期望过高
No. I know things could still go wrong,
我明白  有可能出差错
but if they don't...
但万一顺利
...if this works out,
如果没有问题
we're gonna have a baby. A baby!
我们就会有孩子了  孩子
Yes. But--
是的  但是...
Oh, my God. It's gonna work!
会成功的
We're gonna make it work!
我们会成功的
I'm gonna be a mommy,
我要当妈妈
and you're gonna be a daddy!
你要当爸爸
All right, I'll see you suckers.
回见了  你们这群笨蛋
I'm gonna go get me a baby!
我要去领个娃娃了
Screw it. I'm gonna be a daddy!
管它呢  我要当爹啦
《老友记》第十季第九集 去见孩儿他妈
《老友记》  第十季  第9集 去见孩儿他妈
Hey, who's Phoebe with?
菲比跟谁在一起呢
I wanna say,
我想说
"Someone I'm gonna have sex with."
会跟我上床的姑娘
- Hey. - Hey.
-嘿  -嘿
So who's your friend?
你那朋友是谁啊
Oh, that's Sarah.
那是莎拉
No. Don't you get any ideas.
不  你少打我朋友的主意
I'm not setting you up with
我再也不给你
any more of my friends.
撮合我的朋友了
Why? Why?
为什么  为什么
Because you'll date her once...
因为你约一个睡一个
...sleep with her, then forget she exists.
然后就把人家忘到九霄云外
Name one friend of yours I did that with.
举例说明一下
- Mandy.  - Mandy, huh?
-曼蒂  -曼蒂啊
Really hot blond, big boobs?
金发大胸辣妹
No.
错
Might be why I don't remember, huh?
难怪我记不住她
Do you think I'm someone else?
你好象把我当别人了
Look, I may not have treated
过去我也许
your friends well in the past.
待你朋友不好
But I have grown up a lot.
但我现在成熟多了
Really. Honest. Rach?
真的  是吧  瑞秋
Yeah, believe it or not, it's true.
信不信由你  是真的
I mean, when Joey and I were together...
乔伊和我交往的时候很乖
...he was wonderful.
非常好
He was thoughtful and mature.
体贴成熟
And for the one week that we went out...
我们交往那一周
...he didn't sleep with anybody else.
他都没和其他女人上床
Growth.
成长
Fine, I'll give you her number.
好  给你她的电话号码
Okay. Thank you.
谢谢你
And I promise you I will not forget this one.
我保证我不会忘记这个
- Mandy.  - Sarah!
-曼蒂  -莎拉
Sarah.
莎拉
- Hey.  - Hi.
-嘿   -嗨
Hey.
嗨
Hey, guys, I need some fashion advice.
嗨  给点着装建议
How does this look?
帽子好看吗
Well, it's-- It's a little low. Pick it up a little.
有点...  有点低  戴高点
A little bit more.
再高
There you go.
好了
Now throw it away.
扔一边去
Come on! This looks good.
别这样  这帽子多好看
Ross, please trust me.
罗斯  相信我
I buy 30 fashion magazines a month.
我一个月买30本时尚杂志
Now I don't know who's running for president
我可能不清楚谁想竞选总统
or who that NATO guy is...
或是北约那些人都是谁对谁
...but I do know that
但我知道
you have to get far away from that hat.
你该离那帽子越远越妙
Damn it. God....
见鬼
I have this date tomorrow night,
明晚我要约会
and I have to look cool.
我得扮帅才行
If you need fashion help,
如果你需要着装建议
Rachel and l are going shopping tomorrow.
明天我和瑞秋要去购物
You're more than welcome to come with us.
欢迎同去
Really? That would be great.
真的  太好了
I mean, I have to do something.
我必须有备而去
She kind of teased me about how I dress.
她总是取笑我的衣着
I can see why. Nice shirt.
能看出来  就你那衬衣
You're wearing the same shirt.
你和我穿得一样啊
Gap:美国最大服装公司之一
白痴"盖璞"  什么人都穿
Make yourselves comfortable,
请随便坐
and I'll be back with Erica.
我带艾瑞卡过来
Okay, thank you.
好  谢啦
Well, this is it.
总算到了
Are you okay?
你状态如何
Yeah, it's just weird, you know?
很好  对话会有点奇怪
It's like, "Hi, I'm Chandler.
"我叫钱德勒
May I have the human growing inside you?"
你体内的小人  可以给我养吗"
You're gonna be great.
你会表现出色的
Well, obviously.
那显然
Monica? Chandler?
莫妮卡  钱德勒
I'd like you to meet Erica.
这位是艾瑞卡
Hi.
嗨
Hi. It is so, so nice to meet you.
真高兴跟你见面
- Hi. - Thank you for agreeing to see us.
-嗨   -谢谢你同意见我们
- Hi.  - I'll let you get acquainted.
-嗨   -你们熟悉一下
Okay.
好的
So it's Monica and Chandler?
你们是莫妮卡  钱德勒
I only know you as "File CRW33815-D."
你们的档案代号是"CRW33815-d号"
That's what our friends call us.
朋友们就这么叫我们
Gosh, you know, you're just such an amazing couple. It's...
天啊  你们这一对太令人羡慕了
...kind of intimidating.
都让人有点敬畏
I don't know about that.
你过奖了
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吗
I mean, it's enough that you're a doctor.
我是说  您是医生就够好了
But on top of it, you're married to a reverend?
您竟然还娶了个牧师
I don't think that's exactly--
这不是我们...
Let her finish, doctor.
让她说完  医生
- Hey.  - Hey.
-嗨   -嗨
My friend Sarah had a great time last night.
莎拉昨晚跟你一起很愉快
Yeah.
是吗
Yeah, so you gonna call this one back?
是啊  这次你会再约她吗
No.
绝不
What are you talking about? Sarah's great.
你说什么呢  莎拉很棒
Oh, really? You want to know
是吗  你知道你的很棒的朋友
what your "great" friend did?
干了什么好事
We're out to dinner, okay?
我们出去吃饭
We were getting along,
相处融洽
having a really nice time.
聊得开心
I was thinking she was really cool.
我也觉得她很酷
And then, out of nowhere...
然后  突然间...
That's it?
就这样
That's why you won't go out with her again?
这就是你不想再跟她约会的理由
So she took some fries. Big deal.
不就吃了你的薯条吗  有什么大不了
Hey, look, it's not about a few fries.
我不是气她吃我几根薯条
It's about what the fries represent.
你得清楚薯条的象征意义
- What?  - All food!
-啥  -所有食物
Well, I'm sorry.
对不起
I can't believe I set you up
竟然介绍你
with such a monster!
和这么个"怪物"约会
Hey, look, I take a girl out...
我带女孩吃饭
...she can order whatever she wants.
她点什么都可以
The more the better, all right?
越多越好
Just don't order
但不可以自己
a garden salad and then eat my food!
只点沙拉却夺我的食物
That's a good way to lose some fingers.
这么做有可能被切手指的
Thank God you're here. Listen to this.
谢天谢地你来了  你来评评理
What?
怎么了
Joey and my friend are out last night,
乔伊昨晚约我朋友
having dinner, and she reaches over...
在吃晚饭的时候
- ...and takes a few of his fries--  - Oh, no!
-她伸手拿他的薯条  -哦  不
What?
这有什么
You know about the plate thing?
你知道这条规则
Oh, yeah, yeah. No, Joey doesn't share food.
是是  乔伊从不分享食物
I mean, just last week we were having breakfast...
上星期我们一起吃早餐
...and he had a couple grapes on his plate.
他盘里有些葡萄
You wouldn't let her have a grape?
你不让她吃葡萄
No, not me.
不  不是我
Emma.
是艾玛
Joey doesn't share food!
乔伊从不分享食物
Well, I still think that is a stupid reason
我还是坚持认为就因为这件破事
not to call someone again.
放弃她很不明智
You are calling her, okay?
你再约她  好吧
And if you need to,
如果有必要
then just get an extra plate of fries for the table.
干脆再点一盘薯条不就完了
I like that.
这主意不错
A sharing buffer. Yeah.
共享缓冲区
Yeah, I'll order some extra fries.
多点一盘薯条
Maybe a plate of onion rings.
再点一盘洋葱
Yeah. Yeah.
好  好
And a shrimp cocktail.
还要鸡尾虾
And some Buffalo wings.
再要些辣鸡翅
Maybe.... Maybe an individual pizza, huh?
或许  一个披萨
And some mozzarella sticks.
和炸干酪牛肉棒
What were we talking about?
我们在谈什么
Wow, this place is awesome.
这地方太好了
We should just go.
我们还是走吧
I'm not gonna find anything here.
我在这淘不到什么的
This stuff is ridiculous.
这的东西都太可笑了
Oh, this place is great!
这地方简直太赞了
Rach, come on, I'm not gonna wear any of this.
瑞秋  我才不会穿这个
Nothing silver.
我才不穿银色的
- Why?  - Okay, nothing with hair.
-为什么   -有毛毛的
And nothing with padlocks on it!
更不穿带挂锁的
Ross, look. Look,
罗斯  看看
I know that some of this stuff is out there.
我知道肯定能挑出几件的
But I mean, come on, look at this.
但你看这  看看这个
Look at this sweater.
看看这件毛衣
I mean, this is just beautiful.
你看多好看
Wow, this is really soft.
是很柔软
350 dollars?
350元
Down from 700.
从700块打折下来
You're saving, like, 200 bucks.
你差不多省了200块呢
Both logic and math
今天逻辑学和数学
are taking a serious hit today.
都饱受摧残
Hey, check this out. It's totally you.
这件好  很衬你
Wow. Actually, this looks pretty good.
哇哦  这件看起来不错
Yeah.
是啊
Boys will be boys:舞曲名
《男孩就是男孩》
- What? They will be!  - All right.
-本来就是   -好好
That's it, I'm getting out of here.
算了  我走
No, Ross, wait, come on.
别  罗斯  等等嘛
There's other stuff here.
还有其他的呢
There's some nice shirts, these nice pants.
衬衣和裤子都不错
Actually, these might look pretty good on me.
其实  这些看起来挺适合我
Yes, they will. You know what you should do?
嗯  是的  你知道你应该干嘛么
Go take a walk.
你随便转转先
All right? I know your size,
我知道你尺码,
and I'll pick out some really good stuff for you.
我帮你挑些上等货色
- Really?  - Yes.
-当真   -对
I know what looks sexy on guys.
我知道男人穿什么最性感
Just wear what I suggest,
穿我推荐的衣服
and she is gonna go nuts for you.
不迷死她才怪
So you're saying...
你是说...
...if I wear these pants,
我若穿这条裤子
I might be getting into hers?
她会允许我侵犯
Why do men keep talking to me like this?
为什么男人老跟我来这套
So the fact that I'm a doctor
我是医生
and my wife's a reverend...
我太太是牧师
...that's important to you?
这对你很重要
Yeah. I read some great applications...
是啊  很多申请人都很优秀
...but I thought,
但是我想
"Who better than a minister to raise a child?"
带孩子谁能比得上牧师
Amen.
阿门
Plus, I thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor.
另外  我觉得把孩子交给个医生是很好的
Good hands.
很好的一双手
Healing hands.
疗伤圣手
Reverend, can I ask?
牧师  我能问一下
Does the Bible say anything about adoption?
圣经上对领养孩子怎么说吗
It says, "Do it."
但做无妨
"And behold, she did adopt unto them a baby.
她让他们领养了一个婴孩（模仿圣经句式  原为"你要怀孕生子  可以给他起名叫耶稣"）
And it was good."
此乃善举
- Wow.  - Yeah, wow.
-哇  -是啊  我也哇
I was wondering-- You both have such serious jobs.
我在想  你们工作都责任重大
Would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?
你有时间兼顾孩子和你的教友吗
Oh, no, my flock? My flock is good.
我的教友  我的教友们没事儿
Yeah. My flock pretty much takes care of themselves by this point.
这个时候  我的教友都是自己照顾自己
Good flock. Flock...
好教友  教友...
But being a doctor, that must take up a lot of time.
当医生很花时间吧
Not for me it doesn't.
我的情况不同
So how's everything going in here?
谈得如何
We're great.
太棒了
I think I may have asked all my questions.
我想问题我都问完了
Good. Do you have questions for Erica?
很好  你们有什么要问她
Yeah, actually.
我想问问
So you read a file that you liked...
你读到满意的申请表
...and then you gave the agency the serial number
然后告诉代理人编号
and they contacted us?
然后他们联系到我们
Yes. Our system ensures total anonymity.
我们的系统中用户完全匿名
We're very proud of it.
我们以此为荣
You should be.
应该骄傲
You're really on top of stuff.
真的是一流
Well then, if there's nothing else,
别的没什么了
then the two of us should talk.
那我们俩谈谈
I actually....
实际上…
- I don't think we have to. - We don't?
-我想我们不必谈了 -为什么不
Yeah, when I read about you two,
我看了你们的档案
I was pretty sure I wanted you...
就确定要选你们
...but I just thought we should meet face to face.
但还想当面见见你们
I've made my decision.
我决定了
I choose them.
就选他们
Oh, my God, this is great.
哦  天啊  太棒了
This is so great. Did you hear that?
太棒了  听见吗
Yeah, I did.
是的  听见了
Hey.
嘿
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢  太谢谢了
You are so going to heaven!
你将来一定进天堂
We got some really great stuff.
我们买了些很棒的东西
Yeah.
对
Yeah, but I'm not sure about some of the bras I got.
但是  有些胸罩似乎不妥
Really? Do you want to try some of them on for me?
真的  你能穿上试给我看吗
Okay.
好
Wait, are we in Joey's imagination?
等一下  我们是在乔伊的幻想里吗
Oh, no. I took one of Ross' bags by mistake.
糟糕  错拿罗斯一袋
And one of mine is missing.
我那件不见了
Ross probably has it.
肯定在罗斯那里
You'll get it from him later.
找他拿回来好了
So, what do you think?
你觉得如何
I think we're not wearing the same shirt anymore.
这下我们再也撞不了衫了
Yeah. Yeah, Rachel picked it out for me.
对  瑞秋帮我选的
She told me to trust her, and you know what?
她让我相信她
I'm glad I did.
真高兴我答应了
I turned quite a few heads on my way over here.
一路过来回头率暴高
Dude, I really don't think you should be wearing that.
老兄  别穿成这样
I see.
我明白
Somebody's afraid of a little competition with the ladies?
有人怕我抢走了女人的目光
Looks like someone is the ladies!
看起来好用某人就是个女人了
You're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off.
你嫉妒  因为你不能把这件扒下来
Yeah. Now if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
现在失陪了  我约会去
See? All eyes on me!
看到没  大家都只看我
We are not signing those papers.
不能签
Why not?
为啥
It's wrong. They made a mistake.
这样做不对  他们搞错了
They think we're somebody else.
当我们是别人
God works in mysterious ways.
上帝的安排  凡人懂什么
You have got to stop.
别再冒充了
But she liked us.
但她喜欢我们
She likes Doctor Chandler
她喜欢的是钱德勒医生
and Reverend Monica.
和莫妮卡牧师
If you think about it,
如果你想一下
I'm kind of like a reverend.
我其实满像牧师
I mean, as a chef, I serve God
作为主厨  我给饥饿的人和穷人提供食物
by feeding the hungry and poor.
这不也是为上帝服务
Your veal chop is 34.95!
你们一份小牛排卖34块9毛5
Come on,
得了
I just-- I think we've been given an opportunity.
幸福来敲门了
The mistake's already made.
不如将错就错
They're writing up the papers now.
他们已经在写书面报告了
But we're not the ones she chose.
但我们不是她要选的人
How can you feel okay about this?
你竟然理直气壮
Because.
因为…
We may not be who she thinks we are...
虽然我们不是她选中的人
...but no one will ever love that baby more than us.
但没人会比我们更爱那个小娃娃
- I know.  - I mean, who knows...
-我明白  -我的意思是
...how long it's gonna take for someone else
谁知道我们到底还要等多久
to give us a baby?
才会有人再选我们
What if no one ever picks us?
万一永远没人选我们
Oh, honey....
哦  亲爱的
Please?
求你了
Please. We are so close.
求你了  我们就快要成功了
Monica, I want a baby too.
莫妮卡  我也想要孩子
But this woman is giving away her child.
但她要送出他的心肝宝贝
She deserves to know who it's going to.
她应该知道对方的真实身份
Okay. You're right.
好吧  你说的没错
So we'll tell the truth.
我们告诉她真相
And who knows, you know?
但是谁知道呢
Maybe she'll like us for us.
没准她会因为我们告诉她真相而喜欢我们
Maybe she will.
或许她会
Why couldn't I have been a reverend?
我怎么就不是牧师呢
You're Jewish.
你是犹太教的
Technicality!
差别不大
Garden salad for the lady.
女士点的田园沙拉
Oh, that looks great. Good ordering.
看来很诱人  真会点
Seafood platter for the gentleman,
男士点的海鲜拼盘
and extra fries.
另有一盘薯条
Enjoy.
请慢用
Those fries look delicious.
薯条很美味
I didn't know you liked French fries.
你也喜欢吃法国薯条
Help yourself. What's mine is yours.
吃吧  我的就是你的
Wow, are those stuffed clams?
好大的蒸粉蚌
Yes, they are my stuffed clams.
对  是我的蒸粉蚌
How about those fries, though, huh?
吃薯条如何
- They are delicious.  - Yeah.
-很好吃  -是啊
You are beautiful, you know that?
你真漂亮  知道吗
That is so sweet.
嘴真甜
Okay, then.
好的
Now look what you did!
你捣什么乱
What? What is the matter with you?
什么  不怎么了
I don't like it
我不喜欢
when people take food off of my plate, okay?
别人抢我盘子里的东西吃
But you said, "What's mine is yours."
但你说过"我的就是你的"
Well, I didn't mean it!
我那是客气
Fine. Sorry,
好吧  对不起
I didn't think it was that big a deal.
没想到你这么在乎
No, I'm sorry. I....
不  我很抱歉
I'm overreacting, okay?
是我反应过激了
It's just, when it comes to food, l...
在食物方面
...have certain rules...
我有一些戒律
...okay? I mean...
我是说
...there are things you do,
有些事可以做
and, you know, things that you don't do.
有些事是禁止的
Wow, this place looks great.
这儿很不错
Oh, you are gonna love it.
你会喜欢的
And I'm so glad we're finally doing this.
真高兴我们终于能一起吃饭了
- Me too.  - Here.
-我也是  -我来
So this was fun.
真有趣
I really am sorry about, you know, before.
刚才的事真抱歉
And I want to make sure you know
你一定要知道
I really do like you.
我真的喜欢你
Sure, just not as much as clams.
是啊  但是没有喜欢蛤蚌那么多
Well, stuffed clams....
蒸粉蚌
Chocolate torte for the lady.
女士要的巧克力甜品
Cheesecake for the gentleman.
男士的奶酪蛋糕
Excuse me, sir.
先生
There seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.
我的蛋糕好像有些红的乱七八糟的东西
Yes, that's a raspberry coulis.
是的  那是覆盆子酱汁
I'm so stupid ordering cheesecake,
点奶酪蛋糕真够蠢
trying to be healthy.
还想说吃健康食品
Oh, no.
哦  不
This is work. I should call in.
工作电话  我得复机
Can you excuse me?
失陪
Yeah, sure. No problem.
当然 请便  没问题
What are you doing?
干嘛
I thought you don't share food?
你不是不和人分享食物
Sure I do.
才没有
Coulis?
覆盆子酱汁
No. If I can't have your clams,
不  我都不能吃你的蛤蚌
you can't have my dessert.
你也不能碰我的甜品
This is a two-way street.
规则是双向的
Really?
是吗
Really.
是的
Now this all better be here when I come back.
我回来时希望它完好无损
Yeah, of course. I can control myself.
当然  我能控制自己
Stop staring at me!
别再瞪着我
Just a tiny little....
就一小口
I'm not even sorry.
我甚至不感觉抱歉
- Hi.  - Hey.
-嗨   -嗨
So these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption.
领养的初步手续就这些了
There's a lot to go over,
有很多东西要看
but I'll explain as we go through.
但是过的时候我会一一解释
- Is that a picture? - Yeah.
-孩子的照片   -对
It's a sonogram they took of the baby last week.
是上周给小婴儿拍的B超
I thought you might want to see it.
你们也许有兴趣看看
Look, doctor.
医生快看
Look, before we sign anything,
签字前
we really have to talk.
我们得谈谈
We're not who you think we are.
我们不是你选中的夫妇
I don't understand.
什么意思
The agency must have made a mistake.
领养机构肯定出了什么错
My wife is not a reverend,
我太太不是牧师
and I'm not a doctor.
我不是医生
- What? - That's impossible.
-啊   -不可能
I could perform an operation on you
如果你愿意  我可以替你开刀
and prove it if you'd like.
向你证明
I have to check your file. Excuse me.
我去查档案  失陪
So who are you?
你们到底是谁
Our names really are Monica and Chandler. We're from New York.
我们是叫莫妮卡和钱德勒  纽约来的
Yeah, but the important thing to know about us...
但重要的是
...is how much we would care for this little baby.
我们真的很爱这个小孩
So you lied to me before?
你们先前跟我撒谎
Well, we "bore false witness."
我们"犯了伪证罪"
See? I could be a reverend.
看  我真有当牧师的天赋
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
But we were hoping that since we told you the truth...
我们希望说明真相后
...that you still might consider--
你能网开一面...
Giving you my baby?
把我的宝贝给你们
You think I'd give you my child after this?
发生这一切后  你们以为还会给你们
You don't have to decide now.
不必马上决定
If you look at our file--
请看看我们的档案
I don't want to look at your file. This is over.
没兴趣  到此为止
Erica, wait.
艾瑞卡  请等等
I have nothing to say to you.
我跟你无话可说
Look, you have every reason to be upset.
你有任何理由生气
We did lie.
我们是撒了谎
But only because we've been waiting
但那是因为
and trying to have a baby for so long.
我们想要个孩子等太久了
And we don't know how long it's gonna be
我们也不知道下一个机会
before we get another chance again.
何年何月才会到来
Why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?
让你的牧师祈祷去吧
Erica, please.
艾瑞卡  求你了
Just consider us.
考虑一下我们吧
Ask them to see our file.
找他们要我们的资料
Our last name's Bing.
我们姓宾
My wife's a chef, and I'm in advertising.
我太太是个主厨  我从事广告业
Oh, yeah.
嗯
I actually liked you guys.
我的确喜欢你们
But it doesn't matter.
但已经不重要了
Because what you did was wrong.
你们不该撒谎
But you did like us.
但你喜欢我们对不对
And you should.
你也应该喜欢我们
My wife's an incredible woman.
我太太是个很了不起的女人
She is loving, and devoted and caring.
她有爱心  乐于奉献  关怀他人
And don't tell her I said this,
别告诉她我这么说过
but the woman's always right.
但她一贯正确
I love my wife more than anything in this world.
我爱我太太胜过世上一切事物
And it...
所以...
It kills me that I can't give her a baby.
不能给她个孩子我难受死了
I really want a kid.
我很想要个孩子
And when that day finally comes,
有了孩子以后
I'll learn how to be a good dad.
我会学习如何做是个好爸爸
But my wife...
但我太太...
...she's already there.
她已经是个好妈妈
She's a mother...
她是一个妈妈
...without a baby.
可惜没孩子
Please?
求你了
You still want that baby?
你还想要那个孩子吗
God bless you, Chandler Bing!
上帝保佑你  钱德勒·宾
Turns out this sweater is made for a woman.
原来这件毛衣是女款的
So why are you still wearing it?
那你还穿
Because it's soft.
以为很软和
Hey, so how was your date?
今天过得如何
Not so good.
不太好
Well, looks like it's just the two of us tonight,
看来今晚就我们两个了
huh, buddy?
对吧  哥们
Yeah. And you know what?
是啊  你知道吗
We could do a lot worse.
还有更倒霉的时候呢
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-是阿 -嗯
Joey doesn't share food!
乔伊从不分享食物